All right, four PBJs,
好的，四个花生酱果酱三明治，
three with no crust for the boys,
三个不要面包边给男孩们，
and one weirdly with extra crust for Dawn.
还有一个奇怪地要多加面包边给Dawn。
What? I like to make crustaches.
什么？我喜欢做面包边胡子。
I give you Sir Isaac Gluten.
我授予你‘艾萨克爵士·谷蛋白’。
[applause]
（掌声）
Hey, guys, your dad and I have to work late,
嘿，伙计们，你们的爸爸和我今晚得加班，
so Tanya is gonna pick you up and babysit you tonight.
所以Tanya会来接你们并今晚照顾你们。
[all groaning]
（大家都唉声叹气）
Come on. Not Tootin' Tanya.
拜托，不是‘嘟嘟Tanya’。
Hey, she can't help that she makes those sounds.
嘿，她发出那些声音也是没办法的事。
Those aren't the only sounds she makes.
她发出的声音可不止那些。
She's got a clicky ankle, a poppy knee,
她的脚踝会咔嗒响，膝盖会啪啪响，
and there's always something sloshing around in there.
而且总有什么东西在里面晃荡。
[both shivering]
（两人颤抖）
And she has underarm hairs.
而且她还有腋毛。
That's acceptable in some cultures, buddy.
这在某些文化中是可以接受的，伙计。
In a plastic bag?
用塑料袋？
She knits things from it.
她用它编织东西。
[all shivering]
（所有人颤抖）
Sorry, kids, but Tanya is the only one
对不起，孩子们，但只有塔尼亚
who can survive the quad-nado.
能在这四重龙卷风中幸存。
Remember Pushover Paige?
还记得容易妥协的佩奇吗？
Are you sure this is what your parents meant
你确定这是你父母所说的
by "Sundae dinner?"
“圣代晚餐”吗？
- [growling] - Mm-hmm.
嗯。
Okay.
好吧。
Or Easily Hypnotized Harry?
还是容易被催眠的哈利？
You will take us to the movies.
你会带我们去看电影。
I will take you to the movies.
我会带你们去看电影。
Ooh! And buy us popcorn.
哦！还要给我们买爆米花。
Oh, and buy you popcorn.
哦，还要给你买爆米花。
Sorry, kids, but you're stuck with Tanya.
抱歉，孩子们，你们只能和Tanya在一起了。
You will not let Tanya babysit us.
你不会让Tanya来照顾我们的。
Yeah, that doesn't work on us.
是的，这招对我们没用。
Honey, I don't think we should let Tanya babysit them.
亲爱的，我觉得我们不应该让Tanya来照顾他们。
- Tom.
Tom。
You will change the light bulb on the front porch.
你会换掉前门廊的灯泡。
[exhales deeply] You're getting Tanya.
（深呼吸）你要让Tanya来。
I have to go buy a light bulb.
我得去买个灯泡。
- Uh-oh, I recognize that snap, crackle, slosh.
哎呀，我听得出那咔嚓、噼啪、哗啦的声音。
Good news! Tanya's in the hizzle housie.
好消息！Tanya就在这屋里。
Better news. I shave!
更好的消息。我刮胡子了！
And knit cap for everyone.
还有针织帽给每个人。
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
[all] [whistling melody]
[rhythmic clapping] - ♪ ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR! ♪
♪ ♪
[man] ♪ NA, NA, NA, NA, NA-NA ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐-呐 ♪
♪ NA, NA, NA, NA, NA-NA ♪
- ♪ ONE, TWO ♪ - ♪ NA, NA, NA ♪
- ♪ 一，二 ♪ - ♪ 呐，呐，呐 ♪
[man] ♪ ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR! ♪
♪ 一，二，三，四！♪
Wow, look who's finally awake.
哇，看看谁终于醒了。
How was your night with Tanya?
昨晚和Tanya过得怎么样？
We were up half the night.
我们大半夜都没睡。
She sang us lullabies.
她给我们唱了摇篮曲。
Well, that's sweet.
嗯，真贴心。
About all the things they put in sausage.
关于他们在香肠里放的所有东西。
There's more horn than you would think.
里面的角比你想象的要多。
Nicky, as you know, I am always on a quest
尼基，如你所知，我总是在追求
to improve the products I sell.
改进我所销售的产品。
You see this inflatable raft?
你看到这个充气筏了吗？
Normally, it would take
通常，它需要
a whole 20 seconds for it to inflate.
整整20秒才能充气。
Who's got the time?
谁有时间等？
Exactly!
没错！
That's why I have created
这就是为什么我创造了
the world's fastest inflatable raft.
世界上充气最快的橡皮艇。
This baby inflates in just one second.
这小家伙只需一秒钟就能充好气。
Come on.
得了吧。
It can't be that fast.
不可能那么快。
[air blowing, thumping]
[气流吹动，砰砰声]
Oh, come on.
哦，得了吧。
How come I never get to fly in?
为什么我从来没机会飞进去？
Anne, I have terrible news--
安妮，我有坏消息——
Oh, there he is.
哦，他在这儿。
Ooh, eggs and bacie.
哦，鸡蛋和培根。
Here you go, sweetie.
给你，宝贝。
No, thanks.
不了，谢谢。
I'm still full from Tanya's smelt fish casserole.
我还饱着呢，Tanya的胡瓜鱼砂锅让我撑了。
I thought she made beef casserole.
我以为她做的是牛肉砂锅。
She did, but it smelt like fish.
她是做了，但闻起来像鱼。
Well, there will be plenty more fishy meat.
好吧，还会有更多鱼味的肉。
Your mother and I are going out this Saturday
这周六我和你妈妈要出去，
and Tanya is watching you again.
Tanya会再来看着你。
[all] What?
什么？
It's the Annual Boulder Sporting Goods Store Awards.
这是年度博尔德体育用品店颁奖典礼。
Once again, we have been nominated
又一次，我们被提名
for Best Store With a Rock Climbing Wall
获得最佳设有攀岩墙的商店
and Also a Cafe.
以及咖啡馆的奖项。
And this year, we are bringing home that trophy.
今年，我们要把那个奖杯带回家。
[chuckles]
（轻笑）
[whispers] Whether we win it or not.
（低声说）不管我们是否赢得它。
Hey, why not make Saturday a double win
嘿，为什么不让我们在周六双喜临门
and let us have a sitter who didn't use
让一个没有用
that spatula as a back-scratcher.
那个锅铲当挠背器的人来照顾你们。
Look, I'm telling you.
听着，我告诉你。
Babysitters are not easy to find.
找到好的保姆不容易。
It's not like someone we like and trust
不像是会有我们喜欢和信任的人
is just gonna walk through that door.
会就这样走进门来。
[Josie] Hello?
[乔西] 有人吗？
Hey, Josie. You don't have to knock.
嘿，乔西。你不用敲门的。
- We trust you. - Hey, Mr. Harper.
- 我们信任你。 - 嘿，哈珀先生。
When I was closing last night, I found this bag of cash
昨晚我关门时，在软椒盐卷饼机旁边发现了这袋现金。
next to the soft pretzel machine.
哦，谢谢。[轻笑]
Oh, thanks. [chuckles]
我得给银行打电话。
I need to call the bank.
我可能不小心存了个椒盐卷饼。
I may have deposited a pretzel.
Dad, what about Josie?
She knocks. She returns your money.
And--do you have an itchy back?
- No. - She's perfect!
- Yes! - I know, seriously. Right?
Josie would be a great babysitter,
but I'm sure she's really busy
with school and work and her band.
I would love to babysit.
[all] Yes!
是的！
Not so fast.
别急。
Do you know any lullabies about sausages?
你会唱关于香肠的摇篮曲吗？
No.
不会。
Proceed.
继续。
[all cheering]
（所有人欢呼）
[all giggling]
（所有人咯咯笑）
Wow, you got the cool soccer girls to laugh?
哇，你让那些酷酷的足球女孩笑了？
I've been trying to find an in with them forever.
我一直想找机会接近她们。
What'd you say?
你说了什么？
I just said, "Here you go, ladies."
我只是说，“给你们，女士们。”
Well, did you do an accent, like,
嗯，你是不是用了口音，比如，
[with Cockney accent] "Here you go, ladies!"
“给你们，女士们！”
Or a yodeling voice, like,
还是用了约德尔唱法的声音，像这样，
[singing] "Yodel-adies-hoo!"
“约德尔-女士们-呼！”
[laughs]
（笑）
Dawn, why don't you just go up and say hello.
Dawn，你为什么不直接过去打个招呼。
Yeah.
是啊。
I can do that.
我可以做到。
I say it all the time.
我经常这么说。
Just watch me.
看我的。
Don't do the yodel. Don't do the yodel.
别学约德尔唱法。别学约德尔唱法。
Don't do the--
别学——
[singing] Yodel-adies-hoo!
[唱] 约德尔-艾迪-呼！
I yodeled.
我唱了约德尔调。
Girls, this is Dawn.
女孩们，这是Dawn。
She's terrible at yodeling,
她约德尔唱法很糟糕，
but great at soccer.
但足球踢得很好。
You should get to know her.
你们应该认识她。
See you at your house at 7:00.
晚上7点在你家见。
Coolest babysitter ever.
史上最酷的保姆。
You have a babysitter?
你有保姆？
[scoffs] No.
（嘲笑）才没有。
I'm just saying she'd be cool for babies
我只是说她照顾小孩会很酷
who needed to be sat.
如果那些孩子需要被照看的话。
Then why is she going over to your house?
那她为什么去你家？
Uh, you know, for a hang sesh.
呃，你知道的，就随便玩玩。
So you're just hanging with Josie?
所以你只是和乔西一起玩？
That's cool.
挺好的。
Well, yeah. It is.
嗯，是的。确实是。
You guys should join us sometime.
你们应该找个时间加入我们。
So...
那么...
Soccer, huh?
足球，是吗？
[whispering]
[低语]
So, you want to practice with us tomorrow?
所以，你想明天和我们一起练习吗？
Well, yeah!
嗯，是的！
But why wait till tomorrow?
但为什么要等到明天呢？
My dad just got a new shipment of soccer ball snapbacks.
我爸爸刚收到一批新的足球帽。
[ball thumping]
[球撞击声]
[grunts]
[咕哝声]
Right in the bread basket.
正中要害。
And that complete stranger is testing them out.
而那个完全陌生的人正在测试它们。
[spraying]
（喷洒声）
[coughing]
（咳嗽声）
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
I'm musking up for Josie.
我在为Josie喷香水。
[groans]
（呻吟声）
This is not a date.
这不是约会。
Not with that attitude.
不是以这种态度。
[spraying] [both coughing]
（喷洒声）（两人咳嗽声）
[groans]
Why does it smell like desperation in here?
Come on, guys, if we blow this with Josie,
we're back to Tanya.
[Anne] If they pull anything shiny
out of their pockets, it's a trap.
- If they're noisy, it's a trap. - If they're quiet, it's a trap.
What if they set up an actual trap?
Oh, you'll recognize it, step to the side to avoid it,
and be right in another trap.
These kids are horrible!
这些孩子太糟糕了！
All right. Love you guys.
好吧。爱你们。
Bye, guys. Love you so much. Okay, kiss.
再见，伙计们。非常爱你们。好了，亲一个。
[all] Mommy, I love you.
妈妈，我爱你。
Honey, honey, honey, honey, honey, honey, honey, honey!
亲爱的，亲爱的，亲爱的，亲爱的，亲爱的，亲爱的，亲爱的，亲爱的！
Thank you, Josie. Bye, kids!
谢谢你，乔西。再见，孩子们！
Bye.
再见。
I know your parents are a little worried,
我知道你父母有点担心，
but I got this under control.
但我能控制住局面。
You're in good hands.
你在我这里很安全。
[screams]
[尖叫]
[all scream]
[所有人尖叫]
Got ya! [laughs]
抓到你了！[笑]
You guys were so scared.
你们刚才吓坏了。
So what do we do first?
那我们首先做什么？
I'm gonna check my pants.
我要检查一下我的裤子。
Unrelated to what just happened.
与刚才发生的事无关。
[chuckles]
[轻笑]
So how'd it go with the soccer girls?
和那些踢足球的女孩们相处得怎么样？
Awesome!
棒极了！
We hung out, then they totally
我们出去玩了，然后她们完全
asked me to play soccer with them.
邀请我和她们一起踢足球。
All because of you.
都是因为你。
[chuckles] Stick with me, kid.
（轻笑）跟我混，小子。
I got your back.
我罩着你。
All clear.
一切正常。
[doorbell rings]
（门铃响）
- That's the pizza. - I'll get plates.
那是披萨。我去拿盘子。
Hi, Dawn.
嗨，Dawn。
Denise?
Denise？
Hi! You're at my house!
嗨！你在我家！
Oh, my gosh. You're at my house.
哦，天哪。你在我家。
You said I should come for a hang sesh
你说我应该找个时间和你们一起玩，
with you and Josie sometime.
和你还有乔茜一起。
This is sometime.
这就是那个‘某个时间’。
Is Josie here yet?
乔茜已经来了吗？
Oh, right. Josie and the hang sesh.
哦，对了。乔茜和一起玩的事。
No, she's not here yet.
不，她还没来。
What do you mean? She's babysitting.
什么意思？她在照顾小孩。
Baby-seshing.
小孩聚会。
That's what Josie and me call a very small hang sesh.
这就是Josie和我所说的非常小的聚会。
But it's over now.
但现在结束了。
[groans]
[叹气]
We should do this again sometime.
我们应该找个时间再聚一次。
Not this sometime. Another sometime.
不是这次。是另一次。
But sometime when the soccer girls can be here.
但下次要让足球队的女孩们也能来。
Bummer.
真遗憾。
And they're already here.
而且她们已经在这里了。
Yay.
耶。
[Dawn] And a bunch of other kids.
[Dawn] 还有一群其他的孩子。
Dude, sweet party.
伙计，派对真棒。
[Dawn] Party?
[Dawn] 派对？
Who said there was a party?
谁说有派对的？
Oddly Old-Looking Oscar.
看起来老成的Oscar。
I heard about it on the Interwebs.
我在网上听说的。
We're throwing a party?
我们在办派对吗？
How come I wasn't invited?
为什么我没被邀请？
You're the one who told us not to blow it,
是你告诉我们不要搞砸的，
and you're blowing it?
而你现在却在搞砸？
I'm not throwing a party.
我没有办派对。
And I'm not blowing anything.
而且我什么也没搞砸。
You guys distract Josie.
你们去分散Josie的注意力。
I'll get everybody out.
我会把大家都弄出去。
Hi. [chuckles]
嗨。[轻笑]
Get out.
出去。
Hi. Get out.
嗨。出去。
Dude, this is so awesome.
伙计，这太棒了。
Thank you so much. Get out.
非常感谢。出去。
Think about it. You can't preheat an oven.
想想看。你不能预热烤箱。
You just heat it.
你直接加热它。
You don't heat it before you heat it.
你不能在加热之前先加热它。
[both laughing]
两人都在笑
He says the things we're all thinking.
他说出了我们都在想的事情。
I smell a trap.
我闻到了陷阱的味道。
That's my body spray.
那是我的身体喷雾。
It's called Lady Trap.
它叫做女士陷阱。
Is it working?
它有效吗？
'Cause I'm gonna be straight with you--
因为我打算跟你直说——
I like this.
我喜欢这个。
You guys are funny.
你们真有趣。
Oh, my gosh. It is a trap.
哦，我的天哪。这是个陷阱。
[party music playing]
[派对音乐播放]
♪ ♪
No, no, no. It is not a party.
不，不，不。这不是派对。
Great party.
很棒的派对。
Really?
真的吗？
I mean, I could do way better and I will,
我是说，我可以做得更好，而且我会的，
but on another night.
但不是今晚。
Not tonight.
今晚不行。
[Dawn] Hey, why don't you all come back when the party gets real crazy?
[Dawn]嘿，你们为什么不等到派对真正疯狂的时候再来呢？
[all] Yeah!
是的！
What is going on in here?
这里发生了什么？
Josie!
乔西！
You came back!
你回来了！
Let's crank up the tunes!
让我们把音乐调大！
[air blowing]
（风吹声）
[smushing]
（挤压声）
Beep, beep, beep, beep--
哔，哔，哔，哔——
All right, head straight home.
好吧，直接回家。
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey! Not you four.
嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿！不是你们四个。
On the couch.
坐在沙发上。
Go.
走。
Well, at least I remembered
好吧，至少我记得
the awards aren't till next Saturday.
颁奖典礼是下个星期六。
Yeah, I just wish you remembered
是啊，我只希望你记得
before we walked into that memorial service.
在我们走进那场纪念仪式之前。
Get your tissues out, losers!
拿出你们的纸巾，失败者们！
'Cause the winners are gonna bury y'all--
因为赢家们将要埋葬你们——
[both] Beep, beep, beep.
哔，哔，哔。
We finally gave you guys a chance to replace Tanya,
我们终于给了你们机会来替换Tanya，
and the second we're gone, you throw a party?
我们一走，你们就开派对？
- She threw a party. - I didn't throw a party!
- 她开了派对。 - 我没有开派对！
- It sure looked like a party. - It wasn't a party.
- 看起来确实像派对。 - 那不是派对。
What happened to the party?
派对怎么了？
Man, that kid reminds me of my dad.
那孩子让我想起了我爸。
So you're telling me that wasn't a party?
所以你是在告诉我那不是派对？
No, it just kind of happened.
不是，事情就这么发生了。
I wanted the soccer girls to like, me so I invited them--
我想让足球队的女生喜欢我，所以我邀请了她们——
Oh, well, that's not gonna be a problem
哦，那不会有问题的
because you will not be hanging out with those girls anymore.
因为你不会再和那些女生混在一起了。
That's not fair. I didn't do anything.
那不公平。我什么都没做。
Dawn. They need to know the truth.
Dawn。他们需要知道真相。
It was a party.
那是个派对。
What?
什么？
And I threw it.
而且是我举办的。
[all] What?
什么？
Look, I wanted these kids to think that
听着，我想让这些孩子认为
I was a cool babysitter,
我是个酷保姆，
so I invited some of their friends over.
所以我邀请了他们的一些朋友过来。
I'm really sorry.
我真的很抱歉。
Okay.
好的。
Then, Dawn, it looks like you're off the hook.
那么，Dawn，看来你没事了。
But you--
但是你——
You broke our trust.
你破坏了我们的信任。
I'm sorry, but you can't babysit anymore.
对不起，但你不能再照顾孩子们了。
[kids whining]
孩子们在抱怨
No, guys.
不，孩子们。
This is for the best.
这是为了你们好。
Your mom is right.
你们的妈妈说得对。
Come on, Josie. I'll drive you home.
来吧，Josie。我开车送你回家。
Thank you, Dicky.
谢谢你，迪基。
It's nice to see a young person showing some responsibility.
看到年轻人展现责任感真是太好了。
- Tom. - Yeah.
汤姆。
Oh, not again.
是的。
Dawn, Dawn's Plan is crazy.
哦，又来了。
Yeah, who came up with this?
唐恩，唐恩的计划太疯狂了。
How do you think this is really gonna get Josie back?
是啊，这是谁想出来的？
You guys doubted me when I said
你觉得这真的能把乔茜带回来吗？
raccoons don't like hugs.
你们在我说过浣熊不喜欢拥抱的时候也怀疑过我。
Correction.
纠正一下。
They don't like surprise hugs.
他们不喜欢突如其来的拥抱。
Trust me.
相信我。
This plan's gonna work.
这个计划会成功的。
Josie got in trouble for a party she didn't throw.
Josie因为没开过的派对惹上了麻烦。
Now we're gonna get Tanya in bigger trouble
现在我们要让Tanya因为没开过的派对惹上更大的麻烦。
for a party she didn't throw.
然后就是再见了，Tanya，
Then it's ta-ta, Tanya,
你好呀，Josie。
and hello-sie, Josie.
你打电话给她侄子了吗？
- Did you call her nephew? - I didn't.
我没有。
[in Tanya's accent] But Tanya did.
但是Tanya打了。
I say, come to party. Bring stinky food.
我说，来参加派对。带上臭臭的食物。
[normal voice] Now, let's go get Josie back!
现在，我们去把Josie接回来！
- I'll get Dad's raft. - I'll get Mom's cell phone.
- 我去拿爸爸的筏子。 - 我去拿妈妈的手机。
I've got a score to settle with a raccoon.
我有个账要跟一只浣熊算。
Just be on the lookout for Mom and Dad.
注意看着点爸爸妈妈。
[clattering]
（咔嚓声）
It was dented when I found it.
我找到的时候就已经凹了。
Give me that.
给我那个。
Hey, Josie, we wanted to give you a second chance.
嘿，Josie，我们想再给你一次机会。
Come over in 15 minutes, no sooner.
15分钟后过来，别提前。
P.S. Bring donuts.
附言：带上甜甜圈。
Dicky.
迪基。
You're not the only one with a plan.
你不是唯一一个有计划的人。
The raft is stashed.
木筏藏好了。
[sloshing]
[溅水声]
[Dawn] Tanya's here.
[Dawn] Tanya来了。
[doorbell rings]
[门铃响]
[Tanya] In case the bell doesn't work,
[Tanya] 如果门铃不响，
I'm singing now so you know I am here.
我现在唱歌，这样你就知道我在这里。
♪ Sausage, oh, sausage ♪
♪ 香肠，哦，香肠 ♪
♪ You mystery meat ♪
♪ 你这神秘肉品 ♪
[Tanya] ♪ I grind in the goat horn ♪
[Tanya] ♪ 我在山羊角中研磨 ♪
♪ To make you complete ♪
♪ 为了让你完整 ♪
[all] Tanya!
[所有人] Tanya！
Since you like hat so much,
既然你这么喜欢帽子，
I make you scarf for face.
我给你做了个面巾。
[muffled grunt]
[闷哼声]
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Anne, don't worry.
Anne，别担心。
I called the banquet hall three times to make sure the awards are actually tonight.
我给宴会厅打了三次电话，确保颁奖典礼确实是今晚。
Fine. Oh, do you have money for a cab?
好吧。哦，你们有钱打车吗？
Oh, of course I have money for a cab.
哦，当然有钱打车。
We may have to hit an ATM.
我们可能得去趟ATM机。
Okay, kids. I love you. Bye.
好了，孩子们。爱你们，再见。
- Be good. Bye. - I love you, mommy.
- 要乖哦。再见。- 我爱你，妈妈。
- I love you. - You're leaving now? Okay.
- 我爱你。- 你现在就要走吗？好的。
Honey, honey, honey, honey, honey, honey, honey, honey!
亲爱的，亲爱的，亲爱的，亲爱的，亲爱的，亲爱的，亲爱的，亲爱的！
Okay, bye! Thank you, Tanya!
好了，再见！谢谢你，塔尼亚！
Tanya, we're so glad you're here.
塔尼亚，我们真高兴你能来。
The downstairs toilet is totally clogged.
楼下的厕所堵住了。
Did you bring your plunger?
你带了马桶吸吗？
Does Tanya's milk shake bring the boys to farm?
Tanya的奶昔能吸引男孩们到农场吗？
[laughs]
[笑]
You knows it.
你知道的。
I take care of it.
我来处理。
[Tanya] There is nothing clogged in toilet.
[Tanya] 马桶里没有堵塞的东西。
Nicky, hit it!
Nicky，用力！
[air blowing] [screams]
[吹气声] [尖叫]
[Tanya] Now I'm clogged in toilet!
[Tanya] 现在我被马桶堵住了！
Okay, Tanya-- check.
好的，Tanya——检查一下。
Josie's on her way, and all we need now
Josie正在赶来，我们现在只需要
are the Borschtinyorschkins.
那些Borschtinyorschkins。
[doorbell]
[门铃声]
And sounds like they're at the doorschkin.
听起来他们已经到了门口。
[goat bleating]
[山羊叫声]
[baas]
[羊叫声]
My apologies.
我很抱歉。
My goat here has no manners.
我的山羊这里没有礼貌。
[shouting in foreign language]
[用外语喊叫]
And where is Tanya?
Tanya在哪里？
She left message at meat store
她在肉店留了条消息
saying the family reunion was here.
说家庭聚会在这里。
This is the place. Come on in.
就是这个地方。进来吧。
Ah, I brought aged chicken.
啊，我带了陈年老鸡。
[sniffs]
（嗅）
Okay, shouldn't have done that.
好吧，不该那么做的。
I'm Schtinki. This is my family.
我是Schtinki。这是我的家人。
My wife, Saynya.
我的妻子，Saynya。
And our children, Booshka, Vooshka, Nooshka, and Jill.
还有我们的孩子，Booshka, Vooshka, Nooshka, 和 Jill。
Fellow non-rhymer.
同样是不会押韵的。
Up top.
上面。
[blows raspberry]
（吹口哨声）
Where's the rest of the family?
其他家人在哪里？
[horn blows]
（喇叭声）
[all chattering in foreign language]
（所有人用外语交谈）
All right, everyone.
好了，各位。
Welcome to the Borschtinyorschkin
欢迎来到Borschtinyorschkin家族团聚！
family reunion!
（欢呼声）
[cheers]
大家，安顿下来。放松。
Everyone, settle in. Relax.
我们有来自你们祖国的饮料。
We have punch from your home country.
我们准备了来自您家乡的潘趣酒。
Dicky, you're up.
迪基，轮到你了。
Mom, Dad, Tanya's throwing a party here at the house.
妈妈，爸爸，坦妮娅要在家里办派对。
Come home quick! Bring milk.
快回家！带上牛奶。
It's all part of my plan.
这都是我计划的一部分。
[goat bleating]
[山羊叫声]
[door slamming]
[门砰然关闭]
There's a goat on your porch.
你门廊上有只山羊。
- Josie, thank goodness you're here.
乔西，谢天谢地你来了。
- Where are the donuts?
甜甜圈在哪儿？
Ask the goat.
问山羊。
- Not cool, goat!
不好笑，山羊！
[goat bleating]
山羊叫
[door slamming]
门砰的一声关上
What's going on?
发生什么事了？
Tanya's throwing some crazy party.
Tanya在办一个疯狂的派对。
Mom, Dad, you're here!
妈妈，爸爸，你们在这儿！
What's going on?
发生什么事了？
[all] Hey.
大家：嘿。
[Ricky] Tanya threw a party.
Ricky：Tanya办了个派对。
[Nicky] See?
看吧？
But then Josie came over to get everybody out,
但后来Josie过来把大家都赶出去了，
'cause she's so responsible.
因为她太负责任了。
[Dawn] She's a hero.
她是英雄。
See?
看吧？
A hero who deserves a second chance
一个值得第二次机会的英雄
to be our babysitter.
来当我们的小保姆。
Dawn.
Dawn。
I know you sent me that text.
我知道是你给我发的短信。
And once Josie got your bogus text,
而Josie收到你的假短信后，
she texted us.
她给我们发了短信。
We just wanted to get Josie back
我们只是想让Josie回来
by making it look like she saved the day.
通过让她看起来像是救了场。
Okay. Sorry, everyone.
好吧。抱歉，各位。
The party's over.
派对结束了。
[Anne] Have a good night. Get home safe.
[Anne] 祝大家晚上愉快。安全回家。
[Tom] Thanks for coming.
[Tom] 谢谢大家的到来。
[Anne] Happy reunion.
[Anne] 重逢快乐。
[chattering]
[喋喋不休]
[Nicky] Bye, guys.
[Nicky] 再见，各位。
Ooh. I clean up after goat.
哦，我得清理山羊弄脏的地方。
[distant farting]
（远处放屁声）
What was that?
那是什么声音？
It's Tanya.
是Tanya。
She's in the bathroom.
她在洗手间。
All right, look.
好吧，听着。
I appreciate you guys want me to be your babysitter,
我理解你们想让我当你们的保姆，
but your mom and dad made a decision
但你们的父母已经做出了决定，
and you have to respect that.
你们必须尊重这一点。
[distant fart]
（远处放屁声）
And you shouldn't try to get
而且你们不应该试图让
some poor, innocent woman in trouble.
某个无辜的女人陷入麻烦。
I expected more from you guys.
我对你们期望更高。
[distant fart]
[远处放屁声]
Mom, Dad,
妈妈，爸爸，
Josie didn't invite those kids over the other night.
Josie那晚并没有邀请那些孩子来。
It was my fault.
那是我的错。
- She's right. - Totally her fault.
- 她说得对。 - 完全是她的错。
Josie, is this true?
Josie，这是真的吗？
Yes.
是的。
[distant fart]
[远处的屁声]
But Dawn didn't exactly do it on purpose.
但Dawn并不是故意这么做的。
[fart]
[屁声]
I remember what it's like to be ten,
我记得十岁时的感觉，
desperately wanting to impress the older girls.
迫切想要给大姐姐们留下好印象。
[distant fart]
[远处的屁声]
So I took the blame.
所以我承担了责任。
[distant farting]
[远处的放屁声]
[Dawn] Josie's right.
[Dawn] Josie说得对。
I was bragging about hanging out with her
我当时在吹嘘和她一起玩，
and it just blew up in my face.
然后事情就搞砸了。
[farting]
[放屁声]
If I would have just admitted
如果我当时直接承认
that she was our babysitter in the first place,
她一开始就是我们的保姆，
she'd still be babysitting us.
她现在还会继续照顾我们。
[distant fart]
[远处放屁声]
Josie, we should've known you'd never betray our trust.
乔西，我们应该知道你绝不会背叛我们的信任。
We're sorry.
我们很抱歉。
[farting]
[放屁声]
Okay, what is going on in there?
好吧，里面到底发生了什么？
[panting]
[喘气声]
I had to pop raft to get out of bathroom.
我不得不戳破充气筏才能从浴室出来。
[fart sound]
[放屁声]
[all] Oh!
[所有人]哦！
You know what, Tanya?
你知道吗，Tanya？
We have some bad news.
我们有一些坏消息。
It's okay. I understand.
没关系。我理解。
I hear everything through bathroom door.
我通过浴室门听到了一切。
I take punch, we call it square.
我接受这一拳，我们称之为公平。
Ooh, extra chunky.
哦，特别浓稠。
[farts]
[放屁声]
That was me.
是我放的。
[Dawn] So Josie can babysit us again?
[Dawn] 所以Josie可以再次帮我们照看孩子了？
Hmm.
嗯。
I guess so.
我想是的。
- Yay! - Yes!
- 耶！ - 是的！
[Dawn] Yay. Uh-huh!
[Dawn] 耶。嗯哼！
Yeah.
是的。
Wait, where's Dicky?
等等，Dicky在哪儿？
[panting]
[喘气声]
Dicky, one.
迪基，一分。
Goat, zero.
山羊，零分。
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
♪ ♪
[whistling melody]
[口哨旋律]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪
♪ ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪
- [cheerful melody]
- [欢快的旋律]
- ♪